Hello everyone, welcome back to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我的名字是马可。
And I'm Erica.
我是埃里卡。
And today we're bringing you an advanced lesson for all of our advanced learners out there.
今天我们要为所有高级学习者带来一堂高级课程。
That's right.
没错。
And in this lesson, we're visiting a history class.
在这一课中，我们正在参观一堂历史课。
Yes, we're going to be talking about a very interesting topic that's known around the
是的，我们要讨论一个非常有趣的话题，这个话题全球闻名。
world which is International Workers' Day.
这个世界是国际劳动节。
That's right.
没错。
And we're going to learn a little bit about the history of the workers' movement in the
我们将要学习一些关于工人运动历史的知识。
United States.
美国。
Right, but we're also going to be taking a look at some great words and of course a little
好的，但我们还会学习一些很棒的生词，当然还有一点
bit more advanced or complicated structures.
稍微更高级或复杂的结构。
That's right.
没错。
So I guess without further ado, we can get started with the dialogue.
那么，闲话少说，我们直接开始对话吧。
All right everyone, settle down.
好了各位，安静一下。
Let's get started.
我们开始吧。
As you know, an important aspect of becoming a good citizen is understanding the genesis
正如你所知，成为一个好公民的一个重要方面是理解其起源。
of our legal system.
我们的法律体系。
It's not enough to simply memorize our laws.
仅仅记住我们的法律是不够的。
It's necessary that we comprehend why and how they were formed.
我们必须理解它们形成的原因和方式。
This brings me to our topic for today.
这就引出了我们今天的话题。
Does anyone know what we celebrate on May 1st?
有人知道五月一号我们庆祝什么吗？
Cinco de Mayo.
五月五日节。
No, that's May 5th in Spanish, James.
不，那是西班牙语的5月5日，詹姆斯。
No wonder you're failing my Spanish class.
难怪你西班牙语课会不及格。
No, May 1st is International Workers' Day.
不，五月一日是国际劳动节。
Do we get a day off from school then?
那我们是不是就不用上学了？
No.
不。
It is not considered to be a national holiday here in the US, but in other countries it
在美国，这并不被视为全国性的节日，但在其他国家却是。
is.
是。
Oh man.
哦，天哪。
In the 19th century, working conditions were appalling with workers being forced to work
在19世纪，工作条件极其恶劣，工人们被迫工作。
10, 12, and 14 hours a day.
每天工作10、12甚至14个小时。
Support for the 8-hour workday movement was growing rapidly, despite the indifference
尽管人们对8小时工作制运动漠不关心，但它的支持率仍在迅速增长。
and hostility of many union leaders.
以及许多工会领袖的敌意。
And by April 1886, 250,000 workers were involved in the May Day movement.
到1886年4月，已有25万工人参与了五一运动。
Previous legislative attempts to improve working conditions had failed, so labor organizers
之前的立法尝试未能改善工作条件，因此劳工组织者
took drastic measures.
采取了严厉的措施。
They passed a resolution stating that 8 hours would constitute a legal day's work.
他们通过了一项决议，规定8小时为法定工作日。
And on May 1st, 1886, the resolution took effect.
1886年5月1日，这项决议生效了。
Cool.
酷。
Is that why we only work 8 hours now?
这就是我们现在只工作8小时的原因吗？
Yes.
是的。
But the happy ending came at a high price.
但这个圆满结局付出了高昂的代价。
On May 3rd, 1886, police fired into a crowd of strikers at the McCormick Reaper Works
1886年5月3日，警察在麦考密克收割机厂向罢工的人群开枪，
factory, killing four and wounding many.
造成四人死亡，多人受伤。
A mass meeting was called for the next day to protest the brutality.
第二天召开了一次群众集会，抗议这种暴行。
And then what happened?
然后发生了什么？
Well, as we say, the rest is history.
嗯，就像我们说的，剩下的就是历史了。
All right.
好吧。
So we were in a history class and we learned something new, something interesting, right?
所以我们上了一堂历史课，学到了一些新东西，一些有趣的东西，对吧？
Yeah.
嗯。
International Workers' Day.
国际劳动节。
It's not celebrated in the US, but in many other countries it is.
美国不庆祝这个节日，但许多其他国家都庆祝。
Right.
对。
On May 1st, a lot of people have a day off, so that's always good.
5月1日，很多人放假，这总是好事。
Yes.
是的。
All right.
好吧。
So why don't we take a look at some of the words that we saw in this dialogue, which
那么，我们来看看这段对话中出现的一些单词，
were maybe a little bit different or difficult in Language Takeaway.
这些单词在“语言摘录”部分可能有点不同或难懂。
Language Takeaway.
语言摘录。
All right.
好吧。
We're just going to look at five words here.
我们只看五个单词。
And the first one, we talked about the genesis of the movement.
第一个，我们谈到了这场运动的起源。
Right.
对。
Genesis.
起源。
Okay.
好的。
So many of you may know that Genesis is a book in the Bible, right?
你们很多人可能知道《创世纪》是《圣经》中的一卷书，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
And that's where this word comes from.
这个词就来源于此。
It's the first book in the Bible.
它是《圣经》的第一卷书。
So it's the beginning.
所以它意味着开始。
Or the origin.
或者起源。
Origin.
起源。
So that's a genesis.
所以那就是起源。
The genesis of our legal system, you would say.
你可以说，我们法律体系的起源。
Right.
对。
Or the genesis of this problem.
或者这个问题的起源。
So it's the origin.
所以这就是起源。
Yeah.
是的。
It's a little bit of a formal word, isn't it?
这个词有点正式，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
I guess maybe you can say the origin or the beginning.
我想你可以说“起源”或“开始”。
Yeah.
是的。
But maybe in an academic setting, you can talk about the genesis.
但在学术场合，你可以谈论“起源（genesis）”。
Yes.
是的。
Very good.
非常好。
All right.
好的。
What do we have next?
接下来是什么？
Well, one of the reasons why the workers' movement got started was because of the appalling
嗯，工人运动开始的原因之一是因为骇人听闻的
working conditions.
工作条件。
Appalling.
骇人听闻的。
So if something is appalling...
所以如果某件事是骇人听闻的……
It's shockingly bad.
那就是糟糕得令人震惊。
Very very bad.
非常非常糟糕。
Yeah.
是的。
So now if something is appalling, like the working conditions were appalling...
所以如果某件事是骇人听闻的，比如工作条件骇人听闻……
That's right.
没错。
You would feel appalled.
你会感到震惊。
Exactly.
正是。
I'm appalled at your behavior.
我对你的行为感到震惊。
Okay.
好的。
So it's almost like you are disgusted.
所以这几乎就像你感到厌恶。
Yeah.
是的。
That's right.
没错。
Very very strong word.
非常非常强烈的词。
Yeah.
是的。
Very strong.
非常强烈。
Okay.
好的。
So the working conditions were appalling and people were setting up this movement, right?
所以工作条件骇人听闻，人们正在发起这场运动，对吧？
But what happened?
但发生了什么？
They met some hostility.
他们遇到了一些敌意。
Hostility.
敌意。
Hostility from the police, right?
来自警方的敌意，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
So what is hostility?
那么，什么是敌意？
Hostility is the state of receiving an unfriendly reaction.
敌意是指收到不友好反应的状态。
Okay.
好的。
They acted in a very unfriendly way and it also suggests, you know, a hint of violence
他们表现得非常不友好，而且这也暗示着，你知道，有一丝暴力的意味，
even.
甚至。
Okay.
好的。
Yeah.
是的。
So if somebody is hostile, they can maybe be aggressive and maybe to a point, violent.
所以，如果某人有敌意，他们可能会具有攻击性，甚至可能到暴力的程度。
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
So a hostile person.
所以，一个充满敌意的人。
Yeah.
是的。
Or a hostile environment, a dangerous environment.
或者一个充满敌意的环境，一个危险的环境。
Okay.
好的。
Very hostile.
非常充满敌意。
Very good.
非常好。
Yeah.
是的。
Now because of these appalling working conditions, the labor movement decided to take drastic
现在，由于这些骇人听闻的工作条件，劳工运动决定采取严厉的
measures.
措施。
Drastic measures.
严厉的措施。
Yeah.
是的。
Drastic measures.
严厉的措施。
This is a really wonderful phrase and I think it would help us to listen to a few examples
这是一个非常棒的短语，我认为听几个这个短语在使用的例子会很有帮助。
of this phrase in use.
这个短语在使用的例子。
Example one.
例子一。
The president was faced with some difficult decisions and was forced to take drastic measures
总统面临一些艰难的决定，被迫采取严厉的措施
to solve the crisis.
来解决危机。
Example two.
例子二。
The police took very drastic measures to control the protesters outside the government palace.
警方采取了非常严厉的措施来控制政府大楼外的抗议者。
So we understand drastic measures as extreme actions or decisions, right?
所以我们理解严厉的措施就是极端的行为或决定，对吧？
Yeah, exactly.
是的，没错。
I think there's a saying that says desperate times call for drastic measures.
我认为有句谚语说：非常时期需要严厉的措施。
No, desperate times call for desperate measures.
不，是非常时期需要非常手段。
Dang.
哎呀。
Well, okay, but it goes around there somewhere, right?
好吧，但意思差不多，对吧？
Something like that.
差不多吧。
So if you really have an emergency, you need to do something drastic.
所以，如果你真的遇到紧急情况，你需要做一些极端的事情。
You have to take drastic measures or you can even say take drastic action.
你必须采取严厉的措施，或者你甚至可以说采取严厉的行动。
Okay.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
And what about our last word?
那我们的最后一个词呢？
After the protests ended in violence, people started to get angry because of the brutality
当抗议以暴力结束时，人们开始因为警察表现出的
the police showed.
残暴而感到愤怒。
Okay.
好的。
Brutality.
残暴。
So maybe brutality and hostility are maybe similar, right?
所以也许残暴和敌意是相似的，对吧？
A little bit similar.
有点相似。
So brutality is the state of being harsh or very forceful.
所以残暴是指严厉或非常强硬的状态。
Okay.
好的。
So brutality.
所以是残暴。
Now, we also use the word brutal.
现在，我们也用“brutal”这个词。
Right.
对。
So that means harsh or very forceful.
那意味着严厉或非常强硬。
Now sometimes we can use that word, but not in a harsh or forceful way, right?
有时我们可以用这个词，但不是以严厉或强硬的方式，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
And it's quite, yeah.
而且它挺，嗯。
I might say something like, oh my God, that test was brutal.
我可能会说，哦天哪，那次考试太残酷了。
It was brutal or...
太残酷了，或者……
So it was really hard or really difficult.
所以就是非常难或非常困难。
Right.
对。
So that's what you're saying with this word that it's very hard or it was very intense.
所以这就是你用这个词表达的意思，表示非常难或非常激烈。
Yeah.
是的。
Maybe one more example.
也许再举一个例子。
Okay.
好的。
So for example, I can say, oh, I went for a run today and it was brutal.
比如，我可以说，哦，我今天去跑步了，太残酷了。
I'm so tired.
我太累了。
So it was really difficult.
所以就是非常困难。
Yeah.
是的。
And Marco, is this something that's used by everyone?
马可，这个词是每个人都会用吗？
That phrase, brutal, using in that context would be for younger people maybe.
那个短语“brutal”在这种语境下可能更适合年轻人。
Not really, you wouldn't really hear older people using it.
不太会，你不太会听到老年人用它。
So it's a little bit slangy.
所以它有点俚语化。
Yeah.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
So those are five interesting vocabulary words.
所以这就是五个有趣的词汇。
As Marco mentioned, we want to look at some more difficult structures now in Fluency Builder.
正如Marco提到的，我们现在要在流利度构建部分看一些更复杂的结构。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建部分。
Okay.
好的。
So we have some phrases that we saw in this dialogue and well, let's start with the first
所以我们有一些在这个对话中看到的短语，那么，让我们从第一个开始。
one.
一个。
Well, the teacher opens his discussion by talking about how an understanding of the
嗯，老师通过讨论对法律体系的理解是成为好公民的一个重要方面来开启他的讨论。
legal system is an important aspect of being a good citizen.
法律体系的理解是成为好公民的一个重要方面。
Okay.
好的。
An important aspect.
一个重要方面。
So, well, maybe we know the word important, right?
所以，嗯，也许我们知道“重要”这个词，对吧？
So what's an aspect?
那么“方面”是什么？
Obviously, a part of something, an important part of something.
显然，是某事物的一部分，某事物的重要部分。
Okay.
好的。
So the teacher started with an important aspect of and then specified the idea or what part
所以老师以“一个重要方面”开头，然后具体说明了这个想法或它所属的部分。
it belongs to.
它所属的部分。
Right.
对。
So it usually follows this form.
所以它通常遵循这种形式。
Noun is an important aspect of noun.
名词是名词的一个重要方面。
Okay.
好的。
So for example, quality control is an important aspect of keeping customers happy.
例如，质量控制是保持客户满意的一个重要方面。
Okay.
好的。
Perfect.
完美。
A part of.
一部分。
Very good.
非常好。
So it's a lot more formal or just a lot more intelligent, right?
所以这更正式，或者只是更聪明，对吧？
Yeah, professional.
是的，更专业。
And actually, this is a wonderful way of setting up your idea.
实际上，这是阐述你想法的一个绝佳方式。
So the teacher said that it's an important aspect of understanding the legal system was
所以老师说，理解法律体系的一个重要方面是理解它的起源或开端。
understanding its origins or its genesis.
理解它的起源或开端。
And then she moved on and said that it's not enough to simply memorize laws.
然后她接着说，仅仅记住法律是不够的。
That's right.
没错。
It's not enough to simply do something.
仅仅做某事是不够的。
Okay.
好的。
So the beginning of this sentence, it is not enough to simply something.
所以这个句子的开头是“仅仅做某事是不够的”。
By starting a sentence like this, you are indicating that more is required, right?
以这样的句子开头，你是在暗示需要更多，对吧？
So here, it's not enough to simply memorize the laws.
所以这里，仅仅记住法律是不够的。
We're saying that most people just memorize the laws, but they need to go further.
我们在说大多数人只是记住法律，但他们需要更进一步。
And understand them.
并理解它们。
Exactly.
完全正确。
Another example would be, it's not enough to simply pass your exams.
另一个例子是，仅仅通过考试是不够的。
You must get good grades as well.
你还必须取得好成绩。
Right.
对。
Or maybe in a business context.
或者也许在商业语境中。
It's not enough to simply satisfy your customers.
仅仅让客户满意是不够的。
You must impress them.
你必须让他们印象深刻。
Okay.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
So that's a very good way of starting out this idea of more is required.
所以这是开始表达“需要更多”这个想法的一个非常好的方式。
That's right.
没错。
More is required.
需要更多。
All right.
好的。
Well, I want to move on to one final point here.
嗯，我想继续讲最后一点。
I found this sentence to be really, really interesting.
我发现这个句子真的非常有趣。
They passed a resolution stating that eight hours would constitute a legal day's work.
他们通过了一项决议，规定八小时将构成一个合法工作日。
Okay.
好的。
So why is this interesting?
那么为什么这很有趣呢？
Well, I found that, you know, there's two verbs going on here.
嗯，我发现，你知道，这里有两个动词在起作用。
They passed a resolution that eight hours would constitute a legal day's work.
他们通过了一项决议，规定八小时将构成一个合法工作日。
So we've got two verb times going on here at the same time.
所以我们这里同时有两个动词时态。
And I'm wondering about this one would.
我在想这个“将”字。
Okay.
好的。
So what's happening here?
那么这里发生了什么？
Obviously this happened in the past.
显然这发生在过去。
It's like about a hundred years ago, right?
大约一百年前，对吧？
Right.
对。
So the resolution was passed a hundred years ago.
所以这个决议是一百年前通过的。
Right.
对。
So this is going on in the past.
所以这发生在过去。
Right.
对。
But there was a future action that was going to happen in consequence of this.
但有一个未来的行动将因此发生。
Right.
对。
So the resolution stated that eight hours would constitute.
所以决议规定八小时将构成。
So that's like the primary action was the passing of the resolution.
所以主要行动是决议的通过。
And the result is this sort of this event that happens in the past, but is a future
而结果就是这种发生在过去的事件，但相对于第一个主要事件来说是一个未来事件。
event to the first primary event.
相对于第一个主要事件来说是一个未来事件。
Does that make any sense at all?
这说得通吗？
So this is called the future in the past, right?
所以这叫做“过去将来时”，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
So it's a grammar structure.
所以这是一个语法结构。
Many of you maybe know the simple present or the future tenses, but this is a little
你们很多人可能知道一般现在时或将来时，但这有点奇怪。
strange one.
有点奇怪。
As we said, so maybe it's a little bit difficult to understand the grammar in general.
正如我们所说，所以可能总体上理解这个语法有点困难。
So why don't we take a look at some more examples of how we would use this future in the past.
那么我们为什么不看一些更多关于如何使用这个过去将来时的例子呢。
Example one.
例子一。
The president said that he would cut taxes by 5%.
总统说他将减税5%。
Example two.
例子二。
I made a promise that I would not smoke anymore.
我承诺我不再吸烟。
Example three.
例子三。
Carl told me he would buy a new car.
卡尔告诉我他会买一辆新车。
Okay.
好的。
So now I think it's clear this whole idea of the future in the past and well, we'll
所以现在我认为这个过去将来时的整个概念很清楚了，而且，如果你有任何问题，我们也会在网站上回答，对吧？
also be answering any questions on the site if you have any problems, right?
没错。
That's right.
好的。
Okay.
So why don't we listen to the dialogue one more time and then we'll come back and talk
那么我们为什么不再听一遍对话，然后回来谈谈这个节日，也就是国际劳动节。
about this holiday, which is the International Workers' Day.
国际劳动节。
All right, everyone, settle down.
好了，大家，安静下来。
Let's get started.
我们开始吧。
As you know, an important aspect of becoming a good citizen is understanding the genesis
正如你们所知，成为好公民的一个重要方面是理解我们法律体系的起源。
of our legal system.
我们法律体系的起源。
It's not enough to simply memorize our laws.
仅仅记住我们的法律是不够的。
It's necessary that we comprehend why and how they were formed.
我们必须理解它们为什么以及如何形成。
This brings me to our topic for today.
这引出了我们今天的主题。
Does anyone know what we celebrate on May 1st?
有人知道我们在5月1日庆祝什么吗？
Cinco de Mayo.
五月五日节。
No, that's May 5th in Spanish, James.
不，那是西班牙语的5月5日，詹姆斯。
No wonder you're failing my Spanish class.
难怪你西班牙语课不及格。
No, May 1st is International Workers' Day.
不，5月1日是国际劳动节。
Do we get a day off from school then?
那我们学校放假吗？
No.
不。
It is not considered to be a national holiday here in the US, but in other countries it
在美国这里它不被视为国定假日，但在其他国家是。
is.
是。
Man.
天哪。
In the 19th century, working conditions were appalling, with workers being forced to work
在19世纪，工作条件非常糟糕，工人被迫每天工作10、12和14小时。
10, 12, and 14 hours a day.
每天工作10、12和14小时。
Support for the eight-hour workday movement was growing rapidly, despite the indifference
对八小时工作制运动的支持迅速增长，尽管许多工会领导人漠不关心甚至敌视。
and hostility of many union leaders.
漠不关心甚至敌视。
And by April 1886, 250,000 workers were involved in the May Day movement.
到1886年4月，有25万工人参与了五一运动。
Previous legislative attempts to improve working conditions had failed, so labor organizers
之前改善工作条件的立法尝试都失败了，所以劳工组织者采取了激烈措施。
took drastic measures.
采取了激烈措施。
They passed a resolution stating that eight hours would constitute a legal day's work.
他们通过了一项决议，规定八小时将构成一个合法工作日。
And on May 1st, 1886, the resolution took effect.
在1886年5月1日，该决议生效。
Cool.
酷。
Is that why we only work eight hours now?
这就是我们现在只工作八小时的原因吗？
Yes.
是的。
But the happy ending came at a high price.
但美好的结局付出了高昂的代价。
On May 3rd, 1886, police fired into a crowd of strikers at the McCormick Reaper Works
1886年5月3日，警察在麦考密克收割机厂向罢工者人群开枪，造成四人死亡，多人受伤。
factory, killing four and wounding many.
造成四人死亡，多人受伤。
A mass meeting was called for the next day to protest the brutality.
第二天召集了一次群众会议，抗议这种暴行。
And then what happened?
然后发生了什么？
Well, as we say, the rest is history.
嗯，就像我们说的，剩下的就是历史了。
All right, so Erica, in Canada, do you celebrate this?
好了，那么Erica，在加拿大，你们庆祝这个吗？
We do, but not on May 1st.
我们庆祝，但不是在5月1日。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
When is it?
那是什么时候？
The first weekend in September.
九月的第一个周末。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
And why?
为什么？
Um, I am not 100% sure.
嗯，我不太确定。
I think it's because we already have a long weekend in May, because on the 24th of May
我想是因为我们在五月已经有一个长周末了，因为5月24日是维多利亚女王的生日，所以我们必须庆祝那个。
is Queen Victoria's birthday, so we have to celebrate that.
维多利亚女王的生日。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
So you have two vacations in the same month.
所以你们在同一个月有两个假期。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Well, yeah, I mean, it's not productive, right?
嗯，是的，我的意思是，这不太高效，对吧？
Exactly.
完全正确。
What about in Ecuador?
那厄瓜多尔呢？
Yeah, we do.
是的，我们庆祝。
On May 1st, it's a holiday, and we actually have two holidays in May as well, because
在5月1日，这是一个假日，而且我们实际上在五月也有两个假日，因为在24日，我们庆祝皮钦查战役，这是厄瓜多尔独立的关键战役之一。
on the 24th, we actually celebrate the Battle of Pichincha, which is one of the decisive
皮钦查战役。
battles for the independence of Ecuador.
所以我们不介意在同一个月有两个假日。
So we don't mind having two holidays in the same month.
不介意。
Well, it sounds like Ecuador has a better holiday schedule than Canada.
嗯，听起来厄瓜多尔的假期安排比加拿大好。
So yeah, on May 1st, people take vacations, and our companies usually on May 1st will
所以是的，在5月1日，人们会休假，我们公司通常在5月1日会为员工做些特别的事情。
do something special for their employees.
为员工做些特别的事情。
Oh, that's kind of a nice gesture, isn't it?
哦，那是一种不错的表示，不是吗？
Yeah, so it's like, it's Workers' Day, so they'll set up maybe a barbecue or a trip
是的，所以就像，这是劳动节，所以他们可能会安排烧烤或旅行之类的。
or something like that.
烧烤或旅行之类的。
So that's what usually happens on May 1st.
所以这就是5月1日通常会发生的事情。
Great.
太好了。
Well, what about in your country's listeners?
嗯，那你们国家的听众呢？
Do you celebrate May Day?
你们庆祝五一节吗？
May Day.
五一节。
Yeah.
是的。
May 1st, right?
5月1日，对吧？
And if you do, well, let us know.
如果庆祝，请告诉我们。
Go to EnglishPod.com and leave your questions and comments there as well.
去EnglishPod.com，在那里留下你们的问题和评论。
That's right.
没错。
Thank you for downloading this lesson, and until next time, goodbye.
感谢下载本课，下次再见，再见。